  questionBank = [{
    question: "56(2)(i)",
    correctAnswer: "dividend income",
  },
  {
    question:  "2(22)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "deemed dividend",
  },
  {
    question: "56(2)(ib)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "casual income",
  },
  {
    question:  "casual income",
    grammer: "are in the nature of",
    correctAnswer: "winnings from lotteries, crossword puzzles, races  including horse races, card games and other games of any sort, gambling, betting, etc",
  },
  {
    question:  "56(2)(viii)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "interest received on compensation or enhanced compensation",
  },
  {
    question:  "56(2)(ix)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "advance forfeited due to failure of negotiations for transfer of a capital asset",
  },
  {
    question:  "advance forfeited from AY 2015-16",
    grammer: "will be charged under",
    correctAnswer: "income from other sources",
  },
  {
    question:  "56(2)(x)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "sum of money or value of property received without consideration or for inadequate consideration",
  },
  {
    question: "money received without consideration",
    grammer: "56(2)(x)",
    correctAnswer: "charge on all if money received exceeds 50,000",
  },
  {
    question: "immovable property without consideration",
    grammer: "56(2)(x)",
    correctAnswer: "taxed if stamp duty value exceeds 50,000",
  },
  {
    question:  "immovable property for inadequate consideration",
    grammer: "56(2)(x)",
    correctAnswer: "if consideration is less than stamp duty value (SDV) and the difference exceeds 50,000 and 10% of SDV, then the difference is charged under income from other sources",
  },
  {
    question:  "movable property",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "if consideration is less than fair market value and the difference exceeds 50,000, then the difference is charged under income from other sources",
  },
  {
    question:  "56(2)(x) will not be applicable",
    grammer: "on sum of money or value of property received",
    correctAnswer: ["from any relative", "on the occasion of the marriage of the individual", "under a will or by way of inheritance"],
  },
  {
    question:  "relative",
    grammer: "means",
    correctAnswer: ["spouse", "brother or sister and their spouse", "parents", "brother or sister of either of the parents and their spouse", "any lineal ascendant or descendant and their spouse", "any lineal ascendant or descendant of the spouse", "spouse of any lineal ascendant or descendant of the spouse"],
  },
  {
    question:  "56(2)(xi)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "compensation or any other payment received in connection with termination of employement will be charged under income from other sources",
  },
  {
    question:  "56(2)(xii)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "sum received including bonus, under a LIP other than ULIP and keyman insurance policy, which is not exempt u/s 10(10D)",
  },
  {
    question:  "Keyman Insurance Policy",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "charged under income from other sources",
  },
  {
    question:  "salary of MPs/MLAs",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "charged under income from other sources, except daily allowance and constituency allowance",
  },
  {
    question:  "10(16)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "educational scholarships, entirely exempted",
  },
  {
    question:  "10(17A)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "Awards for literary, scientific and artistic works and other awards by the Government, entirely exempted",
  },
  {
    question:  "10(10D)",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "commuted pension received from a set up by LIC, entirely exempted",
  },
  {
    question:  "115BB",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "tax rate on casual income will be 30% plus HEC",
  },
  {
    question:  "115BBJ",
    grammer: "",
    correctAnswer: "tax rate on winning from online games will be 30% plus HEC",
  },
  {
    question:  "26",
    correctAnswer: "intangible assets",
  },
  {
    question:  "27",
    correctAnswer: "financial reporting of interests in joint ventures",
  },
  {
    question:  "28",
    correctAnswer: "impairment of assets",
  },
  {
    question:  "29",
    correctAnswer: "provisions, contingent liabilities and contingent assets",
  },
];
